parentingweekly.com 2012-10-18

# ParentingWeekly | Privacy Policy

### Privacy Policy

Cord Blood Registry ("CBR") owns and operates this website. This Privacy Policy applies to information that is provided online by site visitors voluntarily on a CBR website, including www.cordblood.com, http://blog.cordblood.com, https://www.cbrgiftregistry.com, https://www.cbrclients.com, https://provders.cordblood.com, http://parentingweekly.com, http://pregnancyweekly.com, http://community.parentingweekly.com, http://babyweekly.com, and http://maternityandstyle.com. Please read the following policy to understand how your personal information will be treated. As our services evolve and we perceive the need or desirability of using information collected in other ways, we may from time to time amend this Privacy Policy. We post the effective date of our Privacy Policy on our website. We encourage you to check our website frequently to see the current Privacy Policy in effect and any changes that may have been made to them. If we make material changes to this Policy we will post the revised Policy and the revised effective date on this website. Please check back here periodically or contact us at the address listed at the end of this Policy.

This policy will let you know:

  1. What personally identifiable information is collected from you
  2. What cookies are and how they are used
  3. How your information is used
  4. Who is collecting your information
  5. With whom your information may be shared
  6. How CBR treats your personal, financial and health-related information
  7. The kind of security precautions that are in place to protect the loss, misuse, or alteration of your information
  8. Editing, Updating, Correcting and Deleting Information About You
  9. What else you should know about your online privacy

What personally identifiable information does CBR collect from me?

CBR collects information in several ways from our websites. In general, you can visit our websites without telling us who you are or revealing any information about yourself, but you are required to enroll in order to obtain access to our services and to certain parts of our websites. By providing your personal information to us, you explicitly agree to our collection and use of such information as described in this Privacy Policy.

If you choose to enroll in newborn stem cell banking on our website CBR asks for certain personal information, including your name, address, e-mail, zip code, credit card, phone, and a portion of a government issued identification number as well as certain health-related information such as the expected due date, your health care plan, delivery hospital and doctor or midwife. Once you enroll, you are no longer anonymous to CBR - you are given a CBR ID and are able to take full advantage of CBR's offerings. When you enroll you will also be asked to set a security question, and will be required to provide the answer for authentication purposes when you log in to your account. 

You may request information about clinical trials without enrolling. If you choose to participate in this feature of our website you will be asked to provide your name, address, email, phone and medical condition in which you are interested. You can also request information from CBR; we may ask for your contact information, due date and other information that will help us assist you. Some information is required while other information may be submitted at your option. Certain websites offer community discussion boards, and you will be asked to provide your full name, zip code, and email address, and to generate a password. You will also be asked to provide your mailing address (although that is not required to set up an account). If you create a personalized start page for certain websites or request a subscription to a one or more of the newsletters offered on a website, you will also be asked to provide your full name, zip code, and email address, and to generate a password.

In addition, we may ask you for personal information at other times, including (but not limited to) when you answer a survey, when you enter a sweepstakes, contest or promotion sponsored by CBR, and when you report a problem with one of our sites or services. If you contact CBR we may keep a record of that correspondence. CBR also occasionally asks users to complete surveys that we use for research purposes. Wherever CBR collects personal information we make an effort to include a link to this Privacy Policy on that page.

CBR also collects information that does not personally identify our site visitors. This may include the visitor's domain name and IP address, but not the email address. This information ("Site Usage Information") is aggregated to measure certain traffic patterns on our websites, such as the number of visits, average time spent on the website, pages viewed, and so on. 

Return to Top

What are cookies and how does CBR use them?

As part of offering and providing customizable and personalized services, CBR uses cookies or similar technology to store and sometimes track information about you. A cookie is a small amount of data that is sent to your browser from a Web server and stored on your computer's hard drive. All areas on CBR where you are prompted to log-in or that are customizable require that you accept cookies. Cookies CBR places will remain in place after you leave our website. You can delete these cookies but this may result in certain features or services not being available to you.

Generally, we use cookies to remind us of who you are and to access your account information in order to deliver to you a better and more personalized service. This cookie is set when you register or "Sign In" and is modified when you "Sign Out" of our services. CBR also uses cookies to store your zip code for demographic and marketing purposes and to measure Site Usage Information, identify websites you have visited, and your visiting patterns in the aggregate.

Return to Top

How does CBR use my information?

The use of your information is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time of use. The provisions contained herein supersede all previous notices or statements regarding our privacy practices with respect to this website. We may use your information internally for our general business purposes, including providing the services you request, responding to your inquiries, and offering you our own, our affiliates' or third-party products and services that we think you may find of interest. We may use your email address to contact you to respond to your inquiries, provide notices to you, or to provide information on products or services to you. CBR may use or include your IP addresses in CBR outgoing email message headers. CBR may use Site Usage Information to measure the use and improve the content of our websites. We may conduct or commission research on our users' demographics, interests, and behavior based on the information provided to us upon registration, during a promotion, from our server log files, from Site Usage Information or from surveys. This information does not personally identify the website users. This research is compiled and analyzed on an aggregated basis. We use this research to better understand how our users' habits are similar to or different from one another so that we can make each new experience on CBR a better one. We may use this information to better personalize the content, banners, and promotions that you and other users will see on our sites. We also may use this information to identify and/or select content that will be presented to you.

Return to Top

Who is collecting information?

When you are on a CBR website and are asked for personal information, you are sharing that information with CBR alone, unless it is specifically stated otherwise. If data is being collected and/or maintained by any company other than CBR, you will be notified prior to the time of the data collection or transfer. If you do not want your data to be shared, you can choose not to allow the transfer by not using that particular service.

Please be aware that CBR advertisers or websites that have links on our site may collect personally identifiable information about you when you visit their websites and/or purchase or use their products or services. The information practices of those web sites linked to CBR are not covered by this privacy policy.

Return to Top

With whom does CBR share my information?

CBR may share aggregated data (which does not personally identify you) with advertisers or business partners, or with third parties that perform services for us. Any user statistics that we may provide to prospective advertisers or partners regarding product or service usage on CBR are provided in the aggregate only and do not include any personally identifiable information about any individual user.

If you provide your healthcare provider's information to us we may disclose personally identifiable information you have provided us to that provider.

We may reveal personally identifiable information about you to unaffiliated third parties if: (1) you request or authorize it; (2) the information is provided to help complete a transaction for you. including, for instance, fulfilling your requests for information from or about our business partners or sponsors or in connection with your participation in a promotion or other event; (3) the information is provided to comply with the law, applicable regulations, court orders or subpoenas, to enforce our Terms and Conditions or other agreements, or to protect our rights, property or safety or the rights, property or safety of our users or others (e.g., to a consumer reporting agency for fraud protection etc.); (4) the disclosure is done as part of a purchase, transfer or sale of services or assets (e.g., in the event that substantially all of our assets are acquired by another party, customer information may be one of the transferred assets); (5) the information is provided to our agents, outside vendors or service providers to perform functions on our behalf (e.g., analyzing data, providing marketing assistance, providing customer service, processing orders, etc.); or (6) as otherwise described in this Privacy Policy.

Return to Top

How does CBR protect my personal, financial, and health-related information? What security precautions are in place to protect the loss, misuse, or alteration of my information?

Keeping your personal, financial, and health-related information private is important to us. There are several places on the CBR site where you can transmit credit card information in order to complete a purchase transaction or for verification purposes. Anytime we ask for a credit card number we transmit that number in an encrypted format. We use industry-standard, SSL (secure socket layer) encryption.

Whenever CBR handles personal information, regardless of where this occurs, CBR takes steps to ensure that your information is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy. We have in place administrative, technical and physical measures aimed at preventing the loss or misuse of the information that you provide to us. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100 percent secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, due to factors beyond our control, CBR cannot ensure or warrant that your personally identifiable information or any other information collected by us will be completely secure from misappropriation by hackers or other third parties or from other criminal activities. Therefore, you provide information at your own risk. 

It is also important for you to help protect against unauthorized access to your information. You are solely responsible for signing off of our Web site each time you finish using it and for securing your log-in information and security responses. Any transactions using your log-in and security responses will be deemed to be authorized by you.

Return to Top

Editing, Updating, Correcting and Deleting Information About You

If you prefer not to receive information from us please let us know by calling us at 1-650-635-4213 or by sending us an [email](mailto:emailus@parentingweekly.com). Please be sure to include your email address, mailing address, full name, and specifically what information you do not want to receive. If you no longer wish to receive any newsletter to which you previously subscribed through this website, or any other communication from CBR, please follow the "opt out" link in the relevant communication, or send us an [email](mailto:cbrclientcare@cordbloodregistry.com).

If you would like to update or correct your email address, mailing address or other personal information with us you may call us at 1-888-932-6568 option 4, email us, or simply edit your information by logging into the "My Account" page of our Web site.

You may also contact us by postal mail at Cord Blood Registry, 1200 Bayhill Drive, San Bruno, CA 94066

Please note that any requests to remove or update your personal information may take up to ten days for your email request and 6-8 weeks to process your postal mail request.

Return to Top

International Use

We control and operate this website from our offices in the United States. Any information you provide to CBR through this website is stored and processed on CBR servers in the United States or on those of our third party service providers. We do not represent that materials on this website are appropriate or available for use in other locations. Persons who choose to access this website from outside the United States do so on their own initiative, and are responsible for compliance with local laws, rules and regulations, if and to the extent applicable.

Return to Top

What else should I know about my privacy?

Please keep in mind that whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information online - for example on message boards, through e-mail, or in chat areas - that information can be collected and used by others. In short, if you post personal information online that is accessible to the public, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return.

This Website is not intended to collect or maintain personally identifiable information from persons under 13 years old. IF YOU ARE UNDER 13 YEARS OF AGE, PLEASE DO NOT USE OR ACCESS THE WEBSITE. If CBR learns that personally identifiable information of a person under 13 years old has been collected without verifiable parental consent, then CBR will take the appropriate steps to delete this information.

Effective Date: October 10, 2011

Return to Top
